while the world takes a pause and more
and more people are losing their jobs or
decreasing their workload and remaining
inside with their families I am going to
be increasing my workload because it is
an essential service right now and I
believe it's within my capacity to do
this even with my limited energy I can
have a conversation I can do live videos
and the world needs what I have to offer
right now
so what I'm committing to doing and I'll
be keep checking in with myself as to
whether I can continue the commitment is
really seeing three videos a week on
this channel on Mondays Wednesdays and
Fridays and whenever the urge calls
other than that so a minimum of three
videos a week I'll be continued to do
the idea cafes on Tuesdays I'm probably
going to alternate between game be
focused idea cafes and coab in 19 and
how it's affecting the world just our
mental health staying inside what we can
be doing topics on that every other week
I I will be continuing my Omega group on
Wednesdays because they are a great part
of my life there is no link to that
those are internal for for us and I will
continue them probably as long as
they're going on that amazing group of
people
I am also still going to be continuing
with the together tech our mega project
our tech cooperative solutions
cooperative that we're figuring out
together Adriel Bentley and I on Fridays
and on Saturdays and we're discussing
ways to bring in more and more people so
that we can have that more meta project
and so I'm still committing to showing
up for those and continue to move our
tech cooperative forward I am focusing
my project in the mega project and
together attack is on solution raising
how we can come together and figure out
solutions that we could create with
10,000 people and $100,000 and so I'm
going to be doing one two three solution
raisings a week on YouTube and on Zoom
uploaded to YouTube and it's its own
Facebook group now and then we're going
to start having the conversations and
how could we actually create some of
these things how can we
get 10,000 people how can we expand the
process so more and more people can get
involved in the in the conversations
without it for being the process and my
new commitment that I will be starting
on Friday although normally it won't be
on Fridays it'll be every day that week
except Friday I will be doing a live
stream of hope sometimes I'm sure it
will not be a pope because I will be
showing up as I am and whoever's our
guests will be showing up as they are
I'm hoping to have guests in the future
because I do better with a conversation
then I do with this broadcast modality
but I'm doing what I can and so from
6:00 to 6:45 all of these times that
I've mentioned are in Pacific Standard
Time if I did mention time for the other
ones is every evening except Fridays I
will be going live from 6 to 6:40 before
going off in order to participate in our
community songs that are happening in my
cohousing community that I'm not living
in Selby strew I'll be joining them by a
streaming and participating in those
which are just so they uplift my soul
and I get to connect with people who I
normally was connecting with multiple
times a week now get to see them at
least on video see their faces and so I
will be going live on youtube and
periscope from 6 to 6:40 every evening
except Fridays where we will be
discussing the possibilities what can we
create with solution raising what is
happening in the world there's nothing
to do with me that people have not even
part of or people that I know what is
currently going on in the world it's
good because we can emerge into a world
that is so much better than what we had
to quarantine from had to start our
quarantine from and so that is what this
channel is what the person who's having
this channel and I'll still be sharing
my internal journey my journey towards
saving the world that now needs it more
than ever so thank you please like and
subscribe at the Bell all those normal
you to be things